starfieldtech.com 2014-06-30

# Starfield Technologies - Starfield Technologies PRIVACY POLICY

Last Revised: November 01, 2011

## Privacy, Security, Your Information

### Starfield Technologies respects your privacy. 

Starfield Technologies has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that its Privacy Policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements, including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@starfieldtech.com](mailto:privacy@starfieldtech.com) or call (480) 624-2500. If you are not satisfied with our response, please contact TRUSTe. 

**Starfield Technologies complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. Users in the European Union consent to the transfer to and processing of their personal information in the United States. We will respond to your request for access to modify or delete your information within thirty (30) days.**

**Other than as described in this Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.**

Information Collection and Use 

Our Site uses forms in which you give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, request information and support, and make product suggestions. For certain services, we may also request a credit card number, government identification number, or other financial information. We will then create an account number for you. 

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone, or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given. 

We use your information to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our Site, new Starfield Technologies services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "Updating Your Information" section below on how to change your preferences. 

We may also use your information to present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates. If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies. 

We use information gathered about you from our Site statistics (for example, your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our Site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system. 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use cookies to identify you so you don't need to log in each time you visit our Site. The cookies are linked to your customer number, which is associated with the information in your account. 

This Site also contains links to other websites. Unfortunately, Starfield Technologies is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

Security 

This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. 

Sending Emails 

We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, as on our [Contact Us](http://starfieldtech.com/contact) page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages. 

Third Party Service Providers 

We may at times provide information about you to third parties to provide various services on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments, serving advertisements, conducting contests or surveys, performing analyses of our products or customer demographics, shipping of goods or services, and customer relationship management. We will only share information about you that is necessary for the third party to provide the requested service. These companies are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using your personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

In the event that we use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gift or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Supplementation of Information 

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third party sources (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Contests/Surveys 

From time-to-time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests or surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose the requested information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age level - note that you must be 18 or above to enter). We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic, and to personalize our Site. 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests. When we do, that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

Targeted Advertisements 

Starfield Technologies may display targeted offers to our customers based on the products currently owned by the customer. These offers will display as varying product banners. There is no personal or geolocation information collected within these product banners to build a profile about your activities or that is shared with third party advertising companies. 

What Happens to my Personal Information if I Terminate my Starfield Technologies Account? 

When your Starfield Technologies account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status on our relevant Starfield Technologies databases. However, deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information as necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements. 

Updating Your Information 

You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following options for changing and modifying your account information or contact preferences. 

  1. You may send an email to [ support@starfieldtech.com ](mailto:support@starfieldtech.com)
  2. You may visit your online Account Manager 
  3. You may send mail to **Starfield Technologies** at the following postal address:   
**14455 North Hayden Road, Suite 219, Scottsdale, AZ 85260 USA**
  4. You may call us at: (480) 505-8800 
  5. You may fax us at: (480) 505-8844 

Transfer of Data Abroad 

If you are visiting this Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement 

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies. 

Changes in Our Practices 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at least thirty (30) days prior to the implementation of the changes. 

Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at: 

Starfield Technologies   
ATTN: Web Team   
14455 North Hayden Rd.   
Suite 219   
Scottsdale, AZ, 85260, U.S.A. 

Revised: November 01, 2011  
Copyright © 2000 - 2011 Starfield Technologies, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
